Charles M. Kurtz
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1843-1940, undated, Series 2:
  - Correspondence, January 11-31, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 1-33)
    (Wm. Stephenson, Charles M. Kurtz, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, February 1-28, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 34-69)
    (Halsey C. Ives, Patty Thum, D.B. Kurtz, Wm. Semple, Robert Ogden-office of John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, March 1-10, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 70-100)
    (Patty Thum, Robert Ogden, D.B. Kurtz, Carl Brenner, L.P. di Cesnola, Stephenson family members)
  - Correspondence, March 11-31, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 101-124)
    (J.M. Wright [for Southern Exposition], M. Knoedler, Wm. Semple, Chas. Sedelmeyer, John Wanamaker, A. Fischhof, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, April 1-15, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 125-144)
    (Chas. Sedelmeyer, Wm. Semple, J.M. Wright, Eliz. R. Coffin, James B. Townsend, The World)
  - Correspondence, April 16-30, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 145-167)
    (Wm. Semple, R.J. Menefee)
  - Correspondence, May 1-7, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 168-194)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, May 8-10, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 195-220)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Wm. Semple, Julia S. Kurtz, Robert Ogden for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, May 11-25, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 221-246)
    (Robert Ogden, Mrs. D.B. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, R.J. Menefee, Edw. Stratton Holloway, D. F. Hasbrouck)
  - Correspondence, May 26-31, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 247-272)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, J. M. Wright)
  - Correspondence, June 1-5, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 273-302)
    (William Semple, Andrew Cowan, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Robert Ogden)
  - Correspondence, June 6-10, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 303-337)
  - Correspondence, June 11-15, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 338-362)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, June 16-20, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 363-387)
  - Correspondence, June 21-31, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 388-432)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 1-5, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 433-462)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, D.B.Kurtz, Wm. Semple, Francis Richards, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 6-10, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 463-495)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Wm. M. Brown, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, July 11-30, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 496-528)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Andrew Redheffer, Charles M. Kurtz, W.W. Thum, S. Wilder)
  - Correspondence, August 1-31, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 529-552)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, September 1-5, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 553-588)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Eugène Fischhof for firm of Chas. Sedelmeyer)
  - Correspondence, September 6-10, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 589-627)
    (Louis Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, September 11-15, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 628-659)
  - Correspondence, September 16-30, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 660-707)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker], Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, October 1-10, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 708-741)
    (Wm. Semple, James Grant [for John Wanamaker], Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, October 11-15, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 742-777)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Eugène Fischhof, James Grant for John Wanamaker], Wm. Thum)
  - Correspondence, October 16-20, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 778-807)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Frederick Dielman, D.B.Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, October 21-31, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 808-852)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Cassel & Co.)
  - Correspondence, November 1-5, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 853-877)
    (G. Klackner, M. H. Wyatt for Chas. Sedelmeyer, Charles M. Kurtz, William Semple, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 6-10, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 878-903)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Fred. P. Kaiser)
  - Correspondence, November 11-20, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 904-932)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S.Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, November 21-30, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 933-967)
    (Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz, William Semple)
  - Correspondence, December 1-15, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 968-996)
    (Stephenson family, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, December 16-31, 1887 (Reel 4808, Frame 997-1029)
    (Stephenson family, Kurtz family, C. C. Ripley)
  - Correspondence, January 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1030-1050)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, T. Addison Richards, Stephenson family, D. B. Kurtz, Louis Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, January 11-20, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1051-1078)
    (Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Stephenson family, Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, January 21-31, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1079-1110)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Stephenson family, James Grant [for John Wanamaker], Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Julia S. Kurtz, James Grant for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, February 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1111-1136)
    (Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz, Walter L. Palmer, R.M. Shurtleff, Eugène Fischhof for Chas. Sedelmeyer, Chas. Sedelmeyer, James G. Tyler, C.Y. Turner)
  - Correspondence, February 11-15, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1137-1161)
    (James Grant for John Wanamaker, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, J.F. Cropsey)
  - Correspondence, February 16-20, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1162-1189)
    (F. E. Bartlett, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, February 21-29, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1190-1222)
  - Correspondence, March 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1223-1286)
    (Geo. H. Story, Julia S. Kurtz, Walter L. Palmer, A.T. Bricher, Wm. Semple, Charles M. Kurtz, H. Siddons Mowbray, Patty Thum)
  - Correspondence, March 11-15, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1287-1311)
    (D. B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, A.P. Ryder, N. H. Carpenter for Art Institute of Chicago, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 16-20, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1312-1339)
    (Thomas B. Clarke, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, S. Wilder, F.S. Church)
  - Correspondence, March 21-31, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1340-1376)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. Semple, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, April 1-5, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1377-1399)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, S. Wilder, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, April 6-10, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1400-1420)
    (T.W. Wood, D.B. Kurtz, Charles, M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, April 11-20, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1421-1458)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Louis P. Dessar, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, April 21-30, 1888 (Reel 4808, Frame 1459-1483)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, May 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 1-34)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Emily Lakey)
  - Correspondence, May 11-24, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 35-65)
    (Thomas Carter, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Stephenson family, D. B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, May 25-31, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 66-99)
    (Robert C. Ogden, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, June 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 100-125)
    (Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Charles M. Kurtz, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, June 11-17, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 126-146)
    (Kurtz family, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Stephenson family, Irving R. Wiles, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, June 18-30, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 147-174)
    (Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Stephenson family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 175-210)
    (J.B. Bristol, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Kurtz family members, Wm. Semple, Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, James Grant for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, July 11-20, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 211-245)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Kurtz family, Chas. G. Loring)
  - Correspondence, July 21-25, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 246-272)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, James Grant for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, July 26-31, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 273-290)
    (Wm. Semple, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, D.B. Kurtz, Chas. Sedelmeyer)
  - Correspondence, August 1-5, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 291-314)
  - Correspondence, August 6-19, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 315-334)
    (Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, August 20-31, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 335-375)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, D. B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, James Grant for John Wanamaker, H.W. Robbins)
  - Correspondence, September 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 376-407)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, September 11-20, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 408-451)
    (Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, James Grant for John Wnaamaker, Alfred C. Howland)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 21-30, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 452-482)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, October 1-5, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 483-509)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, October 6-10, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 510-539)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, E. H. Blashfield, James Grant, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, October 11-20, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 540-578)
  - Correspondence, October 21-31, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 579-614)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 1-15, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 615-641)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Stephenson family, James Grant, Charles M.Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, J. D. Woodward)
  - Correspondence, November 16-30, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 642-690)
    (James Grant, D. B. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, December 1-10, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 691-723)
    (James Grant, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, December 11-15, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 724-752)
    (Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, James Grant, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, December 16-20, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 753-775)
    (James Grant, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, December 21-31, 1888 (Reel 4809, Frame 776-828)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, James Grant, Patty Thum, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, January 1-4, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 829-858)
    (James Grant, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, January 5-10, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 859-885)
    (James Grant, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, January 11-16, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 886-931)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, James Grant, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, January 17-22, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 932-975)
    (James Grant, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, January 24-30, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 976-1030)
    (J. G. Craig, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, February 2-11, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1031-1066)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Patty Thum, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, February 12-19, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1067-1108)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, February 20-28, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1109-1145)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, W.Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 2-9, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1146-1182)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, James Grant)
  - Correspondence, March 11-19, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1183-1218)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Doll and Richards, J.B. Botto)
  - Correspondence, March 20-25, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1219-1241)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Herbert A. Levy)
  - Correspondence, March 27-31, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1242-1258)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, C. Parsons for Harper & Brothers, Charles M. Kurtz, J. C. Nicoll)
  - Correspondence, April 1-10, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1259-1308)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, James Grant, Charles M. Kurtz, Wm. Semple, J. C. Nicoll, Patty Thum, Wm. Semple, Laura Sedgwick Collins, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, April 11-26, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1309-1341)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, M.De Forest Bolmar, D. B. Kurtz, Wm. Semple, Kurtz family, Patty Thum)
  - Correspondence, May 3-16, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1342-1382)
    (John R. Tait, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, May 17-25, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1383-1423)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, James Grant for John Wanamaker, C.E. Haynes-Minneapolis publisher)
  - Correspondence, May 25-31, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1424-1456)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Patty Thum, William Semple
  - Correspondence, June 1-7, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1457-1484)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Geo. H. Smillie, Halsey C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, June 8-17, 1889 (Reel 4809, Frame 1485-1527)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, June 18-30, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 1-68)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, C.E. Haynes-Minneapolis publisher, D.B. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, July 9-25, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 69-89)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Geo. S. Botelieller-Acting Secretary of the Treasury, D. F. Hasbrouck)
  - Correspondence, July 12-18, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 90-126)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Collector's Office, Custom-House, New York City)
  - Correspondence, July 19-21, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 127-141)
  - Correspondence, July 26-31, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 142-171)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Wm. Semple, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, August 1-9, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 172-226)
    (George M. Ciprico, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Laura Sedgwick Collins, Stephenson family, J. H. Dolph)
  - Correspondence, August 10-18, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 227-277)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, August 19-25, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 278-307)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Charles Barnard)
  - Correspondence, August 26-31, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 308-338)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, G.A. McKinstry, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, September 1-9, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 339-375)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Wm. Semple, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, September 10-15, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 376-399)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, September 16-25, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 400-425)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, C. E. Haynes, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, September 26-31, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 426-446)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Thomas Carter, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, October 1-26, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 447-483)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, M. Knoedler & Co., Kurtz family, William Schaus, Patty Thum)
  - Correspondence, November 1-19, 1884 (Reel 4810, Frame 484-518)
    (C.W. Conant, Margaret Lackland Ives, Stephenson family, Kurtz family, D.B. Kurtz, George W. Chambers, Patty Thum)
  - Correspondence, November 20-30, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 519-549)
    (Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz, T. Addison Richards-National Academy of Design)
  - Correspondence, December 1-26, 1889 (Reel 4810, Frame 550-574)
    (Stephenson family, Patty Thum, D.F. Hasbrouck, Sam. P. Avery, James Grant for John Wanamaker, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1890s? (Reel 4810, Frame 575-589)
    (J. B. Botto, W.H. Howe, Clara T. McChesney, Robt. G. Morris, Walter Newbery, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, Jan., 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 590-620)
    (D.F. Hasbrouck, Stephenson family, Kurtz family, Laura Sedgwick Collins, Patty Thum, Thos. W. Wood)
  - Correspondence, February, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 621-638)
    (D.B. Kurtz, F.E. Bartlett, Halsey C. Ives, Kurtz family, Wallace Wood)
  - Correspondence, March, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 639-671)
    (H.C. Ives, Harry Ruseland, E.L. Henry, Patty Thum, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, April, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 672-693)
    (J.G. Craig, Chas. Sedelmeyer, Laura Sedgwick Collins, H.C. Ives, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, May, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 694-717)
    (J. Douglas Moultray-New Zealand artist, H.C. Ives, Albert Bierstadt, Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz, A.T. Bricher, Kurtz family, Robert C. Ogden for firm of John Wanamaker, Charles Sedelmeyer, Laura Sedgwick Collins)
  - Correspondence, June, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 718-760)
    (Charles M. Kurtz for The Tabard Club, D.B. Kurtz, Geo. A. McKinstry, F.E. Bartlett, Kurtz family, Thomas Brower Peacock, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 4-16, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 761-810)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.F. Hasbrouck, D.B. Kurtz
  - Correspondence, July 17-29, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 811-844)
    (Laura Sedgwich Collins, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, H.C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, August 1-20, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 845-880)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Charles P. Tower, H.C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, August 24-31, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 881-911)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Wm. Morgan, Kurtz family, Charles Barnard)
  - Correspondence, September, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 912-936)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, H.C. Ives, Kurtz family, Charles Barnard, W.P. Hanna on behalf of New Zealand artist J. Douglas Moultray)
  - Correspondence, October, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 937-954)
    (Kurtz family, D.B. Kurtz, Lita Rice, A.G. Bullock, Oscar Hammerstein)
  - Correspondence, November 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 955-982)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Charles Barnard, D.B. Kurtz, H.C. Ives, H.W. Ranger, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, December, 1890 (Reel 4810, Frame 983-1040)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Stephenson family, Patty Thum, B.Wells Champney)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-31, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1041-1088)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, A.Dolph, Stephenson, family, Charles Barnard, D. de Vivo, Clara McChesney, D.B. Kurtz, Countess Ella Norraikoff, Wm. Semple, Alice Lakey)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1-27, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1089-1123)
    (James D. Moffat-Washington and Jefferson College, D.B. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Wm. Semple, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, H. c. Ives, L. P. di Cesnola-Metropolitan Museum of Art, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, March 1-31, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1124-1159)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Kurtz family, S.P. Avery, H.C. Ives, F. Rondel, C. de Vivo, T.W. Wood)
  - Correspondence, April 1-12, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1160-1196)
    (H. C. Ives, Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz, Frederick Keppel, Horace R. Johnson, Marcus Benjamin)
  - Correspondence, April 15-27, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1197-1240)
    (H.C. Ives, J. M. Bowles, Charles M. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Wm. Semple, Julia S. Kurtz, Frederick Keppel)
  - Correspondence, May 1-18, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1241-1263)
    (Wm. Semple, Stephenson family, H. C. Ives, D.B. Kurtz, D.F. Hasbrouck, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, May 19-30, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1264-1288)
    (H. C. Ives, Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz, Alice Lakey, Robert Gordon Hardie, Kurtz family, Fred. Schell-Harper & Bros., Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, June 1-11, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1289-1327)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Stephenson family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, H.C. Ives, Kurtz family, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker)
  - Correspondence, June 13-30, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1328-1351)
    (Horace Seeley, Patty Thum, Sam. P. Avery, H. C. Ives, Stephenson family, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 5-17, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1352-1388)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Stephenson family, J. H. Dolph, Patty Thum)
  - Correspondence, July 22-31, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1389-1408)
    (Stephenson family, Patty Thum, H.C. Ives, Elliott Daingerfield)
  - Correspondence, August 2-17, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1409-1440)
    (Marcus Benjamin, Kurtz family, D.B. Kurtz, H.C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Stephenson family, Marie Waloh)
  - Correspondence, August 22-31, 1891 (Reel 4810, Frame 1441-1470)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, H. W. Ranger, Stephenson family, J.H. Dolph)
  - Correspondence, September 1-19, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 1-31)
    (Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz, C.S. Howell, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, September 20-31, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 32-84)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Alf. Trumble-The Collector, C.C. Starkweather-Tock)
  - Correspondence, October 2-12, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 85-133)
    (James Grant for John Wanamaker, Chas. P. Tower, J.H. Lewis, Mrs. H.C. Ives, Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, W.M.R. French-The Art Institute of Chicago, C. C. Starkweather)
  - Correspondence, October 14-18, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 134-160)
    (Sam. P. Avery, Rev.J.D. Spriggs, Chas. P. Tower, Julia S. Kurtz, A. McKinstry)
  - Correspondence, October 19-29, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 161-192)
    (F. E. Bartlett, C. C. Starkweather, Charles M. Kurtz, Montague Marks-The Art Amateur, Marcus Benjamin-D. Appleton & Co., C. de Vivo, Robert C. Ogden for John Wanamaker, Stephenson family, G. Forbes Kelly, firm of Chas. Sedelmeyer, Rev. J.D. Spriggs)
  - Correspondence, November 1-14, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 193-222)
    (Frederick Keppel, Geo. Forbes Kelly-Current Art, C.C. Starkweather, Marcus Benjamin, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 15-19, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 223-250)
    (D.F. Hasbrouck, Marcus Benjamin, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Sam. P. Avery)
  - Correspondence, November 20-23, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 251-289)
    (Marcus Benjamin, Julia S. Kurtz, W.T. Price, Morton Casseday, Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz, Antoinette Van Huesen Wakeman, T.C. No1-firm of S.P. Avery)
  - Correspondence, November 25-30, [November 25-December 6] 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 290-376)
    (Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, J. Douglas Moultray, George M. Ciprico, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, December 7-11, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 377-413)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, H.W. Ranger, Charles M. Kurtz, Holmes Smith-Assistant to Director of St. Louis Museum School of Fine Arts, Tock-C.C. Starkweather, Kurtz family, Mrs. H.C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, December 12-19, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 414-446)
    (C.C. Starkweather, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Clara McChesney)
  - Correspondence, December 21-22, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 447-468)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Patty Thum, Marcus Benjamin-editor, D. Appleton & Co., Montague Marks-editor, The Art Amateur)
  - Correspondence, December 29-31, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 469-485)
    (J. Douglas Moultray, Kurtz family, Marcus Benjamin, Sam. P. Avery)
  - Correspondence, December 23-28, 1891 (Reel 4811, Frame 486-505)
    (E. Fischhof for firm of Chas. Sedelmeyer, Charles M. Kurtz, J.H. Dolph, Geo. McKinstry, D.F. Hasbrouck, F. Hopkinson Smith)
  - Correspondence, probably, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 506-518)
    (H.C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, January 6-10, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 519-553)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, J. H. Dolph)
  - Correspondence, January 11-15, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 554-576)
    (Kurtz family, F.Y.M. Rehn, C.C. Starkweather, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, January 1-5, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 577-623)